Contact

7077908642 (Home) debanjank20@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/debanjankar-3510b2188 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL

Data Analytics

Microsoft Excel

Certifications

The Data Science Course 2019: Complete Data Science Bootcamp

Debanjan Kar

Business Intelligence Specialist | Cerner Corporation | IIITB Bengaluru

Summary

Data Analytics | Retail

I have an overall work experience of 1.9 years in Data Analytics. Currently pursuing Post Graduation Diploma in Data Science with IIIT Bangalore.

Work Summary: Requirement Gathering. Understanding business requirement and mapping data according to business requirement. Exploratory data analysis. Data cleansing, outlier treatment and transformation.

I have worked on various statistical algorithms like Hypothesis Testing, Multiple Linear regression, Logistic Regression, Clustering, Classification, Decision Trees, Random Forest and Optimization Technique Data Visualization using Tableau.

I am proficient in SQL,Python and Tableau.

Experience

Cerner Corporation
Business Intelligence Specialist
April 2020 - Present (5 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka

Accenture

Application Development Associate April 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 10 months) Hyderabad, Telangana

Education

International Institute of Information Technology Bangalore
Post Graduation Diploma in Data Science, Data Analytics and Machine
Learning · (2019 - 2020)

Kalinga Institute of Industrial Technology, Bhubaneswar Bachelor's degree, Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2014 - 2018)